{
        question: 'Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript??',
        choice1: '<script>',
        choice2: '<javascript>',
        choice3: '<js>',
        choice4: '<scripting>',
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question:"What is the correct syntax for referring to an external script called 'xxx.js'?",
        choice1: "<script href='xxx.js'>",
        choice2: "<script name='xxx.js'>",
        choice3: "<script src='xxx.js'>",
        choice4: "<script file='xxx.js'>",
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "How do you write 'Hello World' in an alert box?",
        choice1: "msgBox('Hello World');",
        choice2: "alertBox('Hello World');",
        choice3: "msg('Hello World');",
        choice4: "alert('Hello World');",
        answer: 4,
    },
	{
		question:" Which Command is used to show limited number of commits?",
		choice1:  "git fetch" ,
		choice2: "git log -n ",
		choice3: "git config" ,
		choice4: "git status",
		answer:2,
	},
	{	question: "Which command defines the author email to be used for all commits by the current user.",	
		choice1: "git clean -f ",
		choice2: "git config --global user.email" ,
		choice3: "git merge --no-ff", 
		choice4: "git email--amend",
		answer:2,
	},
	{
		question:" ____________ command is useful for getting a high-level overview of the project history.", 		
		choice1: "git log --oneline",
		choice2: "git reset --hard",
		choice3: "git log --author=''",
		choice4: "git rebase",
		answer:1,
	},
	{
		question:" ___________________ removes untracked files from your working directory",
		choice1: "git commit",
		choice2: "git clean -f",
		choice3: "git clean",
		choice4: "git reset",
		answer:3,
	},
	{
		question:" Which command creates an empty Git repository in the specified directory?",
		choice1: "git reset ",
		choice2: "git log ..",
		choice3: "git init", 
		choice4: "git init --bare", 
		answer:3,
	},
	{
		question: "Command to download all the objects and references from a specified repository",
		choice1:" git config --list",
		choice2: "git help ",
		choice3: "git fetch" ,
		choice4: "git log -n" ,
		answer:3,
	},
	{
		question: "Git command to compare two specified branches",
		choice1: "git diff ...",
		choice2: "git merge", 
		choice3: "git blame -L",
		choice4: "git push --tags",
		answer:1,
	},
	{
		question: "_____________ command renames the current branch to <branch>",
		choice1: "git remote rm", 
		choice2: "git branch -m", 
		choice3:"git branch -D (CAPS)",
		choice4: "git rebase",
		answer:2,
	},
	{	question: "Which Git command displays the patch representing each commit.",
		choice1: "git branch",
		choice2: "git remote -v",
		choice3: "git log -p",
		choice4: "git log",
		answer:3,
	},	
	{
		question: "Which of the following command line environment is used for interacting with Git ?",
		choice1: "Git Bash",
		choice2: "GitHub",
		choice3: "Git Boot",
		choice4: "Git Lab",
		answer:1,
	},
	{
		question: "In Git, if you want to make your local repository reflect changes that have been made in a remote (tracked) repository, you should run the pull command",
		choice1: "True",
		choice2: "False",
		choice3: "Maybe",
		choice4: "Neither",
		answer:1,
	},
	{
		question: "If you want to make radical changes to your team’s project and don’t want to impact the rest of the team, you should implement your changes in -",
		choice1: "the root",
		choice2: "a tag",
		choice3: "the trunk",
		choice4: "None of the above",
		answer:4,
	},
	{
		question: "The Git clone command does which of the following?",
		choice1: "Makes a local copy of the repository",
		choice2: "Creates a working directory",
		choice3: "Commits a new branch",
		choice4: "Both 1 & 2",
		answer:4,
	},
	{
		question: "Which one of the following is not part of the data structure of a Git repository?",
		choice1: "Branch pointer",
		choice2: "Body element",
		choice3: "Commit object",
		choice4: "Head pointer",
		answer:2,
	},
	{
		question: "Which of these Git client commands creates a copy of the repository and a working directory in the client’s workspace.",
		choice1: "checkout",
		choice2: "clone",
		choice3: "import",
		choice4: "update",
		answer:2,
	},
	{
		question: "Git is a .................... Version Control tool.",
		choice1: "Decentralized",
		choice2: "Centralized",
		choice3: "Emphasized",
		choice4: "Customized",
		answer:1,
	},
	{
		question:" GIT belongs to the............. generation of Version Control tools",
		choice1: "2nd",
		choice2: "3rd",
		choice3: "4th",
		choice4: "5th",
		answer:2,
	},
	{
		question: "The main objectives of Git are -",
		choice1: "speed",
		choice2: "data integrity",
		choice3: "support for distributed non-linear workflows",
		choice4: "All of the above",
		answer:4,
	},
	{
		question: "What language is used in Git?",
		choice1: "C",
		choice2: "HTML",
		choice3: "PHP",
		choice4: "C++",
		answer:3,
	},
	{
		question: "Git command .................... used to give tags to the specified commit.",
		choice1: "git checkout [branch name]",
		choice2: "git show [commit]",
		choice3: "git tag [commitID]",
		choice4: "git rm [file]",
		answer:3,
	}